PAUL: Hello.
你好
Welcome to this very special extended holiday
欢迎来到这个特殊的长假集
edition of Supercharged.
来自“增压”
I'm Paul.
我是保罗
SANTA LEWIS: Santa Lewis here, ready for Christmas.
在这里“圣路易斯”准备圣诞节
PAUL: Santa, hey?
你好，圣诞老人。
I recognize that name.
我知道那个名字
And this is the show where I take the sites that you've
这是程序的网站
submitted, and I go through them, and I try
你提出并浏览了，我尝试
and find and fix performance issues.
查找并修复性能问题
And today is no different.
今天也一样
Yay, Merry Christmas.
圣诞快乐
It's Slack, that's what we're going look at today.
这就是我们今天要研究的
I like Slack an awful lot, and we have a Chromium Dev Slack,
我非常喜欢Slack，我们为Slack开发了Chrome。
which will be the target for our performance profiling today.
这将是我们今天的绩效考核目标
So when I said to them, is there anything
当我问他们时，有什么事吗
in particular that you're seeing and that you
您注意到的具体
think that we should look at?
而且您认为应该对其进行检查？
And they went, oh yeah, actually, there's
他们回答，是的
this Quick Switcher.
这个适配器很快
If you hit Command-K, it takes a long time for it
如果按“ Comand-K”，则需要很长时间
to come up on screen and we don't really know why.
在屏幕出现之前，我们不知道原因
Fair enough.
好吧
OK.
我们将从这里开始并在工作中
I think there might be a few other things that we
我认为有几件事
see along the way.
我们在路上看到的
It's bumper.
这很多
This is the right time of year to give you extra.
这是一年中的更多时间
I mean, look in the stocking.
我的意思是看袜子里面
What's there?
那里有什么？
Oh, scrolling issues.
滚动问题
Oh, what's in there?
还有什么？
Layout thrashing.
拥堵图
Oh, worst Santa ever.
有史以来最糟糕的圣诞老人
Bring me the mince pies.
他们带来了水果馅饼
So what we'll do, we will hit Record.
我们要做什么，我们将按记录
And we're going to hit Command-K.
然后按“ Command-K”
And then we'll stop recording.
那我们就停止录音
Yes.
是的
And we see the keydown event over here.
并在此处查看Keydown事件
And they are absolutely right.
他们是绝对正确的
It is just shy of half a second in JavaScript terms
在JavaScript方面仅落后半秒
here for the keydown event.
按键事件
So the keydowns mean pressing Command-K and it coming up
“ Keydown”表示您按“ Command-K”
on screen.
他在屏幕上的样子
So let's have a look at why.
让我们来看看为什么
Well, I see these red triangles in the corner
我在角落看到这些红色三角形
and I see a Recalc Style followed by a Layout.
我看到一个算术图案，后面是一个图表
So, calculating styles on the page,
如果是这样，请计算页面上的样式
followed by laying out elements on the page, followed
元素的布局后面是页面
by calculating styles on the page,
然后计算页面上的样式
and then laying out the elements on the page, which
然后，在页面上布置项目
seems superfluous at best.
这似乎太多了
And actually, each one of these is really quite expensive.
实际上，每一个看起来都很长
Like, this first one is 93 milliseconds
首先是93毫秒
in calculating styles.
在计算模式时
So if we click on it, here you see
因此，如果我们单击它，您可以在此处看到
just shy of 9,000 elements have been
少于9,000个项目
affected by the style change.
受到风格变化的影响
That's an awful lot of elements that could
这是本来可以
If you're going to make some style changes,
如果您要进行一些样式更改
it is often quite good to be very specific about the styles
谨慎对待模式通常会很好
that you want to apply.
你想申请
But it may just be that there is a lot of elements being added
但这可能是因为添加了太多元素
in this case, say to the page.
在这种情况下，对于页面
For example, the Quick Switcher elements.
例如，快速转换器元件
And that might be what the issue is,
那可能是问题
because it's preceded by a parse HTML,
因为它之前是“ HTML”分析
so that makes me think there's new HTML coming in.
这使我认为将出现一个新的“ HTML”
It has its style calculations, and then we
他有自己的风格计算，
force a layout as well.
然后我们也输入布局
Same kind of deal, except this has
一样，除了
got 13,000 elements in play.
13,000名员工
And again, 93 milliseconds.
再说93毫秒
And this is a fast desktop machine.
这是一个快速的设备
This would be brutal on other devices.
这种情况在其他设备上将很困难
So, big problem here then, I guess.
我相信我们有一个大问题
Now the good news is, underneath we actually
现在好消息，我们开始
start to get the Call Stacks.
请参阅召回包
So, we can actually start to figure out why.
我们可以看到为什么
What was it that was called into that
所谓的
was triggering this problem?
那是什么原因呢？
And this is it, here.
这是这里
Clicking on, apparently, this anchor with bugsnag,
通过单击带有图形“ bugsnag”的钩子
I'm not sure what the deal is there.
我不确定这里的主题是什么
But it goes to JQuery-- something to do with that,
但是他去了“ JQuery”，与此有关
I'm not sure what that is.
我不确定这是什么
And then bootstrap with its modal.
然后以其形式启动
And then the Modal show, Modal backdrop.
然后是“模态展示，模态背景”
OK.
好吧
And then, eventually, it seems to trigger and show.
然后最后，它似乎开始显示
So something in this interplay between the rollup
此“汇总客户端”交互中的内容
client, the rollup core, and the bootstrap.
和“汇总核心”并启动
Now, it's going to be very specific to them.
现在对他们来说非常具体
Let's have a quick look at Modal show, just out of interest.
出于好奇，让我们快速看一下“模范秀”
And it's minified.
微型的
So again, for them, I'd say you would just obviously
所以我再次告诉他们，只有你
go to your unminified and have a look around,
您将检查所有不是微型的东西
do the same thing again.
再做一次
But if we start to see things like, yeah, addClass,
但是如果我们开始看到添加类之类的东西
we're making a style change.
我们正在改变风格
We're basically making style changes.
我们基本上是在改变风格
Yeah, we're reading a class here, hasClass("fade"),
所以我们在这里读了一堂课，有一个“消失”课
addClass.
新增类别
So, you start to sort of build up this picture
所以，您有点开始制作这张照片
fairly quickly that there's a check on styles
快速扫描图案
followed by mutation of styles.
然后更改样式
And then if somewhere later in that Call Stack somebody
然后在这个“调用堆栈”中的其他地方
else is reading a style and then writing
读取模式然后写入
a style, that's exactly what's going
模式，这正是发生的情况
to land us in this problem.
让我们陷入这个问题
I'd say it's their code.
我会说这是他们的代码
So I would say, look, go and have a look at this.
我建议你去看看这个
The Call Stacks are here.
呼叫堆栈在这里
They will recognize their own code, I'm sure.
我敢肯定，这将识别他们的代码
And then it's a case of trying to pick it out
然后是选择阶段
and say, well, we should do all our reads up front,
我们说，很好，我们应该首先阅读它
then all our writes.
然后我们所有的写作
Libraries like fasttime will do that for you.
像“ Fasttime”这样的库为您做到了
But you can still do it yourself.
但是你可以做到
Just make sure that you're orchestrating your code
只要确保您安排好代码
very carefully.
非常小心
It can be tricky-- and that's why fasttime exists, because it
您可能会上当，所以有“快速”
will help you do that.
为了帮助你做到这一点
And a lot of people use it very successfully.
许多人很好地使用它
So, that would be how I'd start for them.
这将是我对他们的第一个建议
But, while I was here, I noticed this Update Layer Tree,
但是由于我在这里，所以我注意到了幻灯片更新树
that comes straight after.
在他之后
Updating the Layer Tree is how Chrome organizes basically
更新幻灯片树是“ Chrome”的组织方式
all the layers in the page, so where
页面上的所有幻灯片
everything needs to sit in relation to everything else.
一切都应该连接
And that's 73 milliseconds.
这是73毫秒
That's monstrously long, really long.
太久了
And again, especially so for such a powerful device.
同样，这是针对如此强大的设备
So, what's going on?
那会怎样呢？
Well, layers is the answer, but how
好吧，幻灯片就是答案，但是如何
do we find out more about this?
了解更多？
Well, we have a tool.
好吧，我们有一个工具
We have a Chrome Dev Tool.
我们的Chrome开发工具
That's why it's called Chrome DevTools.
因此，它被称为“ Chrome开发工具”
Tools inside the tools.
工具中的工具
Switch on the paint profiler, hit Record again,
要打开颜色选择器，请再次按记录
and what we'll do is we'll do a bit of a scroll.
而我们要做的是一点滚动
And I can tell you that that is pretty bad.
我可以告诉你这很不好
We have to wait.
我们必须等待
When we've got the paint profiler on,
当颜色选择器打开时
there's an awful lot of extra information that's coming in,
输入大量信息
so it does take a long time to pull that data in
因此提取数据需要很长时间
and actually parse it and get it ready for us to have a look at.
并分析并准备检查
So we have to do the happy dance.
所以我们必须跳起幸福的舞
[SINGING] It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas everywhere
圣诞节开始无处不在
you go.
你去找他
Ah, it's here.
在这里
So what we can do is we can see, yeah, six frames a second,
我们现在看到的是每秒6帧
five frames a second.
每秒5帧
And that's with that paint profiler on.
这是颜色选择器正在运行时
So it'd probably be nearer nine, 10 frames a second,
每秒约9或10帧
certainly not the 60 frames a second that we'd want.
当然不是每秒60帧，这是我们想要的
So, if we click on the Layers-- the frames, sorry, at the top--
如果我们单击幻灯片，则很抱歉，在顶部
we get this Layers tab that we can click into.
查看可点击的幻灯片标记
This layer information is not yet available,
该细分市场的信息目前不可用
but it does come up eventually.
但它确实出现了
Here we go.
我们走了
And we can make this a bit bigger.
我们可以将其扩大一点
And we start to see what all the layers are
我们开始看看幻灯片是什么
that's all these boxes on the screen.
屏幕上所有的盒子
And I'll tell you what we'll do is we'll just move ourselves
我会告诉你我们要做什么，我们只是要搬家
back, and we can spin this out into 3D space.
返回，我们在3D空间中展示出来
Woo hoo.
太好了
Who doesn't love that?
谁可能不喜欢它？
Nobody.
没有人
There we are.
我们走了
Rotate.
转弯
Get back.
回去
There we are.
我们走了
Look at that.
看这个
That's great, isn't it?
很好，不是吗？
It looks like basically every single item in the Quick
似乎转换器的每个元素都很快
Switcher is getting its own layer.
他得到了自己的切面
And that's going to be expensive to manage, I would imagine.
我认为这将很难控制
We can confirm that, though, because what we can do
可以肯定，因为我们可以做
is we can hit Escape, and we would
是按“ Escape”，我们可以
go to the rendering options.
我们去显示选项
If they're not there for you, then
如果他们不在那
you can go to More Tools, Rendering Settings, like that.
我们可以转到“更多工具”，然后转到“显示设置”
And you can switch on Show Layer Borders.
我们可以打开幻灯片边框视图
And, yep, sure as we would expect,
是的，当然如我们所料
each one of these items in the list has got its own layer.
每个元素都有其自己的细分
And, in fact, even the status icon inside
实际上，即使状态图标也在里面
has also got its own layer.
它有自己的细分
And we can spin this down as well, and inside the omnibox,
我们也将其记入“多功能框”中
which is what that is.
那是那个
Yeah, there we are, omnibox_item and then the presence-- so,
在这里，我们进入“ omnibox_item”，然后出现
basically the status.
如果是这样的话
Now, if we click on one of these items,
现在，如果我们单击这些元素之一
we can see the reason that it got its own layer.
我们可以看到她为什么拥有自己的筹码
"Scroll parent is not an ancestor."
通过父母不是亲戚！
No idea.
我不知道
"Might overlap other composited content."
它可以替代其他复合内容
Now that one I can guess.
我猜那些
That's basically something's got a layer,
这是有它自己的东西
and one of these list items might overlap it.
其中之一可以替换
OK.
好吧
And then it says, "Cannot be squashed because this layer has
然后您说，您无法压缩它们，因为该芯片
a different clipping container than the squashing layer."
它具有用于压力支架的不同刀架
Yeah.
太好了
This one took me a long, long time
那花了我很长时间
to figure out when I was looking at this.
要了解它，当您寻找这些
I was like, oof, yeah.
你很绝望
Maybe I'll have to speak to a Chrome engineer.
也许可以和Chrome中的工程师谈谈。
And I was like, just, what?
然后我说，什么！
And they gave me a few hints and got to the bottom of it,
他们给了我一些指示，我明白了
which is good.
哪个好
It's kind of is it going to work out?
能行吗
Who knows.
谁知道
It was an exciting time for me, it was.
这对我来说是令人兴奋的时刻
And always like that with performance work,
他对表演作品一向如此
you get thrown something and you're like, do some forensics.
你得到一些东西并做一些测试
Will you solve the puzzle?
你会解决难题吗？
Who knows?
谁知道
[WHISPERING] It's very exciting.
令人兴奋
That's why I do this.
这就是为什么我这样做
To be or not to be?
是还是不是？
That is the question.
那是问题
Whether 'tis nobler in the mind to suffer the slings and arrows
人的灵魂耐心一点更合适吗
of outrageous fortune, or to take arms
命运之箭或武器毁抵抗
against a sea of troubles.
在麻烦中
And by doing so.
面对
Back to the task at hand.
回到我们的使命
Well, it turns out if you look at the container element-- had
如果您查看容器元素，它会出现吗？
to scroll up for that apparently-- there's
我必须向上滚动
a lot of them, there's a lot of them.
有很多很多
I'm going to get there eventually.
我终于到了
Got there.
来啦好啦
omnibox_results is the container element
“ omnibox_results”是容器元素
that's doing the scrolling.
卷动
It has width, it has a height, but it
它有宽度和高度，但是
has overflow-y: scroll and overflow-x: hidden.
滚动条中有剩余Y，隐藏了有剩余X
So, it's clipping that list, which is great.
所以她削减了名单，这很棒
That's what we'd want it to do, and that makes perfect sense.
这就是我们想要发生的事情，这非常合乎逻辑
However, every single item inside the list,
但是，每个元素都在列表中
it too has overflow: hidden.
他也有盈余隐藏
So, each item is clipping with its contents.
如果每个元素削减其内容
And what blink does is it goes, well,
那你眨一下？好吧
that's got its own clipping because it's overflow: hidden.
这有一个特别的部分，因为盈余被隐藏了
And that clip doesn't match the parent's clip.
这与基本作品不符
Therefore, I'm just going to assume
所以我猜
that it has to have its own layer because of that.
她拥有自己的细分
So, if we switch off overflow: hidden on the children,
因此，如果我们消除孩子们隐藏的剩余
all those layers disappear.
所有这些幻灯片都将消失
and we're going to get one big layer, which
我们会得到一大笔
is probably going to be better.
可能会更好
We'll switch on the timeline again, switch off the paint
我们将再次运行时间表并停止
profiler so that it doesn't take all the extra information we
颜色选择器，以免占用所有其他信息
don't need, and we'll record, and we'll scroll.
我们不需要的，我们将记录并通过
Ah.
好吧
Now we're getting something like 30 frames a second.
现在我们每秒获得约30帧
So we're up from about-- well, it
好吧，我们上去..好吧
was five, six, could be nine or 10 without the paint
没有分隔符的5或6可能是9或10
profiler-- up to about 30.
颜色..到大约30
So definite improvement by having,
因此，我们的收购取得了一定的进展
in this case, one larger layer rather than
在这种情况下，使用一个大芯片代替
hundreds or thousands of smaller layers.
数以百计的小幻灯片
But that's still not 60 frames a second,
但这不是每秒60帧
which is what we'd want.
我们想要的是
So, I see a lot of purple in this chart at the top,
我在这张桌子的顶部看到很多紫罗兰色
and certainly that matches up with,
这当然对应于
yeah, about 12 milliseconds here of Update Layer Tree,
大约12毫秒的树木开发幻灯片
which is down from 20-odd, 24, 25, I think, to 12.
那下降到20或24，我认为是25
So it's definitely better, but it's still not good.
他真的好些，但他还是不好
It should be a fraction of a millisecond, ideally speaking.
理想形状应该大约一毫秒
So let's see if we can figure out what's going on.
那么让我们看看是否可以看到发生了什么
Well, again, we can switch on the paint profiler,
同样，我们可以运行颜色选择器
do a quick run, and see what's what.
快速运行，看看会发生什么
All we need is one of these frames.
我们需要的只是这些轮胎之一
We'll go and wait for the layers.
我们去等待幻灯片
There we go.
我们走了
And we can actually see the list there.
我们可以在这里看到列表
We'll reset the transform.
我们将重置更改
You see the list of items in the Quick Switcher
您将在快速转换器中看到项目列表
and, yeah, you see here.
是的，你会在这里看到
It's 66,266 pixels high.
高度为66.266像素
That's enormous.
好大
That's a huge layer that needs to be handled.
这个巨大的芯片需要调整
And it's just probably putting blink under pressure.
可能会暂时增加压力
We can prove that, I think, by going through to the elements.
我们可以通过检查项目来证明这一点
What we'll do is we'll select the omnibox item,
我们要做的是选择“多功能框”元素
and we will say display: none.
我们会说表演：没事
And that's going to give us nothing in the list, which
这不会在列表上显示任何内容
is not so great.
那不好
But what we can do is we can go and we
但是我们能做的就是走
can override that for a few of them,
并报废其中一些
and so that we've got something to scroll.
直到我们有东西要传递
This is going to take us a minute or two.
这需要一两分钟
So, we've got a few in the list now.
好吧，我们现在有一些名单
So we've enabled like 10 of them, or something like that.
我们跑了十个
And so this list is basically nothing like the size it was.
清单的大小不同
And we'll do another timeline recording,
我们将记录另一个时间表
and we'll swtich off the paint profiler here.
我们将在此处关闭颜色选择器
We'll just have a go without.
没有它我们将努力
And stop that.
别这样
And, yeah, we're basically at 60 frames a second now.
好吧，我们现在得到60 fps
And the Update Layer Tree's gone from that 12,
更新了12个树状幻灯片
13 milliseconds down to three milliseconds.
13毫秒至3毫秒
So clearly the size of that layer is a big, big factor.
显然，芯片的尺寸是一个重要因素
But, that still bothers me because it's still
但这仍然困扰着我，因为它仍然
three milliseconds and it should be a fraction of a millisecond.
3毫秒，大约应该是毫秒
So, something outside of this Quick Switcher
如果快速转换器之外的东西
is probably causing an issue too.
也会造成问题
And my hunch is, having looked at this before,
我的直觉告诉我，在我检查完之后
is it's going to be the actual content of the page.
这将是实际的页面内容
In fact, we can confirm that, because what we could do
实际上，我们可以确认这一点，因为我们可以做
is we could do a paint profile, and we
是确定颜色
will do a quick scroll of the page content.
我们将快速滚动页面的内容
It is 60 frames a second.
每秒60帧
So, we could stop here and that would be OK.
我们可以在这里停下来，这会很好
But, I would imagine that since this Update Layer Tree is still
但是我认为芯片组更新树仍然
quite big, we should see if we can figure it out.
太好了，所以我们必须看看该怎么做
And, yeah, so looking at this, the actual page dividers,
·查看分页符
we got msgs_scroller_div is 12,544 pixels.
我们有“ msgs_scroller_div” 12.544像素
And the actual day divider, which
和主要的分隔符
seems to be the previous day's content, that is 12,000 and so,
看起来像以前的内容约12,000
again, and by 10,000.
秒和10,000
So those are huge layers.
这些都是很棒的切片
And you can see that, actually, here if we get rid of that
如果我们摆脱了这个，我们可以在这里看到
and we zoom out.
走开
There we go.
我们走了
Yeah, there's the actual page in the bottom corner,
这是下角的页面
and this is what it is.
就是这样
There we are.
我们走了
That's what it actually looks like.
那才是真正的样子
There's the page content.
这是页面的内容
We have another one here, and the footer,
我们这里还有另一个，利润也
as well, for reasons I'm not quite sure why.
由于某种原因，我不确定
But it seems to be that it is massive as well.
但是看起来也很大
So, I guess, if I were them, for this and the Quick Switcher,
我认为如果您使用的是快速转换器
I would say, go to something that's like a recycler view
我将使用“回收者视图”之类的内容
where you've got a few much smaller DOM
在哪里可以获得更小的DOM
and you're recycling elements.
然后您回收物品
That means that the layout should be cheaper,
这意味着该方案将更简单
the style calculations should be cheaper,
样式计算应该更简单
everything should be cheaper.
一切都应该更简单
And you can use something like requestIdleCallback
您可以使用类似“ requestIdleCallback”的名称
to only do those mutations to the DOM
只是为了对DOM进行更改
when the user's in idle, and if you need to put up a spinner
当用户放慢速度并想要添加加速器时
or something like that, OK.
或类似的东西
But, maybe you need to take a slightly more nuanced approach
但是也许您应该对它有所不同
where you use requestIdleCallback.
您在哪里使用“ requestIdleCallback”
Or, if it's getting quite pressing,
还是他们要求快速解决方案
you just do it immediately, and you take the hit,
马上就做，并感到震惊
and maybe you froze for second or just waver a little bit.
您可能会被冻结片刻或变得虚弱一些
But it's certainly going to be a lot, lot better than having
但是肯定比得到更好
this huge set of layers that is just putting blink
如此大量的筹码只会增加压力
under pressure here.
一会儿
So, there you go.
所以，你在这里
A bunch of stuff.
很多东西
The Layers panel, the paint profiler,
幻灯片调色板，颜色检查器
just DevTools in general, and scrolling performance issues.
一般的开发工具以及滚动性能问题
Definitely want to take a look at this holiday season.
你应该看看这个假期
Woo, yeah.
哇
If you find yourself with scrolling performance issues
如果滚动有问题
and it's not something like paint,
颜色不是
it might be something like your layers.
它们可能是细分
Check that out.
检查一下
Have a great holiday, and I'll see you in 2016.
祝您假期愉快，2016年见！
It's exciting.
很热情
Brand new year.
新年
It's a leap year.
年